<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guests on Membership Guide</title>
    <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/guests/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guests on Membership Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/guests/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Children Policy</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/children-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:37:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/children-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your children are welcome at Civic Hall for the occasional need. Please be mindful that Civic Hall is designed as a work environment. When you have children here, as with all guests, please be aware of noise levels, food, use of space, and general behavior so to be considerate of the other members of our community. Our Community Space was not designed for children to be present other than for specific events to which they are invited, or for the occasional urgent childcare need. In either event, you are responsible for your child&amp;rsquo;s behavior while here and should make sure they act in a way that does not affect the professional use of the space by other members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please notify us in advance when you require to have your child (anyone under 16 years of age) here by contacting our Community Team at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:community@civichall.org&#34;&gt;community@civichall.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Policy</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/guest-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:28:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/guest-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Members can have a guest in the space for up to 3 hours at no charge. If you need your guest to stay past 3 hours, you will be charged a $35 day pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All guests must sign in when they arrive, and sign out when they leave. If your guest leaves and does not sign out, we will assume they stayed past the 3 hour limit and your account will be charged $35 for a day pass.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>