<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference Rooms on Membership Guide</title>
    <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/conference-rooms/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conference Rooms on Membership Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/conference-rooms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do I Reserve A Conference Room? What does it Cost?</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/reference/conference-room-booking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 10:33:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/reference/conference-room-booking/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;All conference rooms and phones rooms must be reserved. Members can use phone rooms at no additional charge for up to 2 hours per day. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;using-the-booking-calendar&#34;&gt;Using The Booking Calendar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log into your membership portal: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fcivichall.spaces.nexudus.com%2F&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF0ID0nKHKNlX1W_Ha_Iv1D2XxxVw&#34;&gt;civichall.spaces.nexudus.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From the Civic Hall pull down menu in the top right, then select “Booking Calendar”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure you are looking at correct date you would like to book the resource then click on the empty box that corresponds with the resource and time you would like to reserve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Resource&amp;rdquo; refers to all of the rooms that are bookable in the Civic Hall space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upon clicking on the empty space, the “Make A Booking” dialog box will appear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the Dialog Box, you will be able to adjust the resource time frame (keep in mind all rooms are only available for a minimum of 15 minutes and a &lt;strong&gt;max of 2 hours per day&lt;/strong&gt;. You will be able to add a meeting title or notes regarding your booking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you click save booking your reservation will be added to the calendar and you will receive a confirmation email.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will have up to 1 hour prior to your booking to cancel and make changes. &lt;strong&gt;After that you will be responsible for the charges.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;conference-and-meeting-room-prices&#34;&gt;Conference and meeting room prices:&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>