<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Membership Benefits on Membership Guide</title>
    <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/membership-benefits/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Membership Benefits on Membership Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/membership-benefits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack Community</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/membership/slack-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 07:43:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/membership/slack-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Slack network is an excellent platform to communicate and stay in touch with all of your fellow Civic Hall members. In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic Hall Slack Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; we post events outside Civic Hall, share exciting member news, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shortly after your membership was approved, you should have received an email with an invitation to join the Slack channel. Create your login and you’re in. If you never received the invite, check your spam folder. If you still can not find it, email community@civichall.org and we will resend your invitation. Please make sure to provide an active email address.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambassadors</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/membership/ambassadors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 13:08:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/membership/ambassadors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Civic Hall Ambassador is &lt;strong&gt;your link between the business of Civic Hall and the community of Civic Hall&lt;/strong&gt;. Every member of Civic Hall is assigned an Ambassador during their first week of membership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ambassadors use their own experiences to provide you with an idea of what it is like to be an active and engaged member of the community. They will be initiating introductions, sharing information, and elevating ideas for events, programs &amp;amp; activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are unsure of who your Ambassador is, please email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:community@civichall.org&#34;&gt;community@civichall.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>