<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Animals on Membership Guide</title>
    <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/animals/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Animals on Membership Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Pets, Dogs, Cats or Other Animals Allowed At Civic Hall? Are Service Animals Allowed?</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/reference/animals-at-civic-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 08:44:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/reference/animals-at-civic-hall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Domestic pets that are not licensed service animals are not permitted at Civic Hall.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An employee, or a member, who requires the help of a service animal (defined by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.law.cornell.edu/cfr/text/28/36.104&#34;&gt;28 CFR 36.104&lt;/a&gt; as &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;any dog that is individually trained to do work or perform tasks for the benefit of an individual with a disability&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;) will be permitted to bring a service animal to the workspace, provided that the animal’s presence does not create a danger to others and does not impose an undue hardship upon the company.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pet &amp; Service Animal Policy</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 08:15:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/pets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Civic Hall is responsible for assuring the health and safety of all. In keeping with this objective, Civic Hall has formulated a policy balancing these concerns with the desire to promote a positive experience by allowing appropriate service animals in the workspace. A service animal may be allowed in the workspace if its health and behavior are acceptable within a business setting, and if it does not adversely affect business operations. &lt;strong&gt;Domestic pets that are not licensed service animals are not permitted at Civic Hall.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An employee, or a member, who requires the help of a service animal (defined by 28 CFR 36.104 as &amp;ldquo;any dog that is individually trained to do work or perform tasks for the benefit of an individual with a disability&amp;rdquo;) will be permitted to bring a service animal to the workspace, provided that the animal’s presence does not create a danger to others and does not impose an undue hardship upon the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The following animals may not be brought to the workplace:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sick animals; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;animals with fleas or any disease that is communicable to other animals in the office or to humans; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;animals that have not been properly vaccinated, or that have internal or external parasites; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dogs that bark or behave aggressively; or &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;animals that foul the inside or outside of the building. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An employee, or a member, who brings a service animal to the office is completely and solely liable for any injuries or any damage to personal property caused by the service animal. Any repair or cleaning/maintenance costs incurred by an animal will be charged in full to the owner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pet-free Zones&lt;/strong&gt;
Service animals are not permitted in the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community Cafe &amp;amp; Stage Area &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kitchen Area &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phone Rooms &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Left Work Zone (in front of lockers) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lounge Area (next to lockers) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All service animals must be in the continuous full control of their owners.&lt;/strong&gt;
They should be in the physical presence of the owner or an appropriate designee at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All dogs must be leashed at all times.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All animals must be comfortable being around people (other than its owner) and around other animals. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADDITIONAL GUIDELINES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Prepared&lt;/strong&gt;
Make sure that if you bring your dog in to work, that they have everything they will need throughout the day. Whether that is their favorite toy, food or a bed, make sure that they will be well accommodated so you can work through the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clean Up After Your Animal&lt;/strong&gt;
Bring detergent and plastic baggies with ties for taking care of dog poop. And if your dog has an “accident” inside the office or office building, be prepared to clean it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vaccinations&lt;/strong&gt;
Owners must be prepared to provide proof of vaccinations to designated Civic Hall staff at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objections&lt;/strong&gt;
Any individual with a grievance regarding an animal at the office should bring the matter to the attention of the owner and/or the Civic Hall staff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insurance&lt;/strong&gt;
Civic Hall may, at its discretion, require the service animal owner to maintain a liability insurance policy covering damage or injuries caused by the animal while at the office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic Hall shall not be liable for loss of, or injury to, any animal brought to the office. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://membership-guide.civichall.org/uploads/reference-nyc-service-animals.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>