<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Guidelines &amp; Policies on Membership Guide</title>
    <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community Guidelines &amp; Policies on Membership Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Pet &amp; Service Animal Policy</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 08:15:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/pets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Civic Hall is responsible for assuring the health and safety of all. In keeping with this objective, Civic Hall has formulated a policy balancing these concerns with the desire to promote a positive experience by allowing appropriate service animals in the workspace. A service animal may be allowed in the workspace if its health and behavior are acceptable within a business setting, and if it does not adversely affect business operations. &lt;strong&gt;Domestic pets that are not licensed service animals are not permitted at Civic Hall.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An employee, or a member, who requires the help of a service animal (defined by 28 CFR 36.104 as &amp;ldquo;any dog that is individually trained to do work or perform tasks for the benefit of an individual with a disability&amp;rdquo;) will be permitted to bring a service animal to the workspace, provided that the animal’s presence does not create a danger to others and does not impose an undue hardship upon the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The following animals may not be brought to the workplace:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sick animals; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;animals with fleas or any disease that is communicable to other animals in the office or to humans; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;animals that have not been properly vaccinated, or that have internal or external parasites; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dogs that bark or behave aggressively; or &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;animals that foul the inside or outside of the building. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An employee, or a member, who brings a service animal to the office is completely and solely liable for any injuries or any damage to personal property caused by the service animal. Any repair or cleaning/maintenance costs incurred by an animal will be charged in full to the owner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pet-free Zones&lt;/strong&gt;
Service animals are not permitted in the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community Cafe &amp;amp; Stage Area &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kitchen Area &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phone Rooms &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Left Work Zone (in front of lockers) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lounge Area (next to lockers) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All service animals must be in the continuous full control of their owners.&lt;/strong&gt;
They should be in the physical presence of the owner or an appropriate designee at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All dogs must be leashed at all times.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All animals must be comfortable being around people (other than its owner) and around other animals. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADDITIONAL GUIDELINES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Prepared&lt;/strong&gt;
Make sure that if you bring your dog in to work, that they have everything they will need throughout the day. Whether that is their favorite toy, food or a bed, make sure that they will be well accommodated so you can work through the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clean Up After Your Animal&lt;/strong&gt;
Bring detergent and plastic baggies with ties for taking care of dog poop. And if your dog has an “accident” inside the office or office building, be prepared to clean it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vaccinations&lt;/strong&gt;
Owners must be prepared to provide proof of vaccinations to designated Civic Hall staff at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objections&lt;/strong&gt;
Any individual with a grievance regarding an animal at the office should bring the matter to the attention of the owner and/or the Civic Hall staff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insurance&lt;/strong&gt;
Civic Hall may, at its discretion, require the service animal owner to maintain a liability insurance policy covering damage or injuries caused by the animal while at the office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic Hall shall not be liable for loss of, or injury to, any animal brought to the office. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://membership-guide.civichall.org/uploads/reference-nyc-service-animals.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 23:52:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Membership at Civic Hall means that the collaboration center, workspace, activities, events, and digital forums:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are a safe and respectful environment for all participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;are a place where people are free to fully express their identities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;presume the value of others. Everyone’s ideas, skills, and contributions have value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don’t assume everyone has the same context, and encourage questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;find a way for people to be productive with their skills (technical and not) and energy. Use language such as “yes/and”, not “no/but.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;encourage members and participants to listen as much as they speak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;strive to build tools that are open and free technology for public use. Activities that aim to foster public use, not private gain, are prioritized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;prioritize access for and input from those who are traditionally excluded from the civic process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;work to ensure that the community is well-represented in the planning, design, and implementation of civic tech. This includes encouraging participation from women, minorities, and traditionally marginalized groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;actively involve community groups and those with subject matter expertise in the decision-making process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ensure that the relationships and conversations between community members, the local government staff and community partners remain respectful, participatory, and productive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide an environment where people are free from discrimination or harassment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:transparent&#34;&gt;Civic Hall reserves the right to ask anyone in violation of these policies not to participate in Civic Hall membership, network activities, events, and digital forums.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic Hall&amp;rsquo;s Anti-Harassment Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All Civic Hall members, network activities, events, and digital forums and their staff, presenters, and participants are held to an anti-harassment policy, included below.&lt;br /&gt;
Civic Hall is dedicated to providing a harassment-free experience for everyone regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, age, or religion. We do not tolerate harassment of members, staff, presenters, and participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any Civic Hall event or network activity, including talks. Anyone in violation of these policies may expelled from Civic Hall membership, network activities, events, and digital forums, at the discretion of the Executive Staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harassment includes but is not limited to: offensive verbal or written comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, religion; sexual images in public spaces; deliberate intimidation; stalking; following; harassing photography or recording; sustained disruption of talks or other events; inappropriate physical contact; unwelcome sexual attention; unwarranted exclusion; and patronizing language or action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a participant engages in harassing behavior, the organizers may take any action they deem appropriate, including warning the offender or expulsion from Civic Hall membership, network activities, events, and digital forums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are being harassed, notice that someone else is being harassed, or have any other concerns, please contact a member of the Executive Staff immediately. You can contact them at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:leadership@civichall.org&#34;&gt;leadership@civichall.org&lt;/a&gt;. The Civic Hall Executive Staff will be happy to help members and/or participants contact security or local law enforcement, provide escorts, or otherwise assist those experiencing harassment to feel safe for the duration of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you cannot reach an Executive Staff member and/or it is an emergency, please call 911 and/or remove yourself from the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also contact Civic Hall about harassment at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:community@civichall.org&#34;&gt;community@civichall.org&lt;/a&gt; and feel free to use the email template below. Civic Hall staff acknowledge that we are not always in a position to evaluate a given situation due to the number of events and the fact that our team is not always present. However, we are hopeful that by providing these guidelines we are establishing a community that jointly adheres to these values and can provide an environment that is welcoming to all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We value your attendance and hope that by communicating these expectations widely we can all enjoy a harassment-free environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email Template for Anti-Harassment Reporting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SUBJECT: Safe Space alert at [LOCATION/EVENT NAME]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing because of harassment at a Civic Hall community space location/event, (NAME, PLACE, DATE OF EVENT).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can reach me at (CONTACT INFO). Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HDMIs, Chargers, Adaptors, etc...</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/misc-electronic-equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:39:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/misc-electronic-equipment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All members are allowed to borrow cables, chargers, and other supplies we may have available at the welcome desk. You will be asked to sign out whatever you request and return it before you leave for the day. Guests of members can not sign out equipment or supplies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitors</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/monitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:39:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/monitors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We ask that you do not move monitors if they have been hardwired.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference, Meeting &amp; Phone Rooms</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/conference-meeting-rooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:39:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/conference-meeting-rooms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All conference rooms and phones rooms must be reserved. View details on how to use the booking calendar in our FAQs section.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:38:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/kitchen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the wonderful assortment of mugs and glasses in our kitchen for coffee, tea, and water. Please return them to the dishwasher when you are done with them and do not leave anything in the sink. If the dishwasher is full, please wash your own dishes by hand and place them on the drying rack/mat. The refrigerator will be cleaned out every evening at 7pm. All items left after 7pm will be discarded. Due to limited space, there are no exceptions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Issues</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/security-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:38:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/security-issues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emergencies - Please call 911 immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lingerers&lt;/strong&gt; - If you notice someone lingering after an event make sure to let them know that they are not allowed to be in the space if they are not members. They must leave once the event is over.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Workspace</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/your-workspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:38:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/your-workspace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please be mindful of the cleanliness of your workspace, and clean up after yourself and your guests. Food trash should be disposed of immediately in one of the many trash and recycling containers distributed throughout the space. Pitching in is part of the culture here at Civic Hall and we encourage everyone to do their part in maintaining a great home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children Policy</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/children-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:37:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/children-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your children are welcome at Civic Hall for the occasional need. Please be mindful that Civic Hall is designed as a work environment. When you have children here, as with all guests, please be aware of noise levels, food, use of space, and general behavior so to be considerate of the other members of our community. Our Community Space was not designed for children to be present other than for specific events to which they are invited, or for the occasional urgent childcare need. In either event, you are responsible for your child&amp;rsquo;s behavior while here and should make sure they act in a way that does not affect the professional use of the space by other members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please notify us in advance when you require to have your child (anyone under 16 years of age) here by contacting our Community Team at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:community@civichall.org&#34;&gt;community@civichall.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Policy</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/guest-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 14:28:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/guest-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Members can have a guest in the space for up to 3 hours at no charge. If you need your guest to stay past 3 hours, you will be charged a $35 day pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All guests must sign in when they arrive, and sign out when they leave. If your guest leaves and does not sign out, we will assume they stayed past the 3 hour limit and your account will be charged $35 for a day pass.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/guidelines/events/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a collaboration center, we will often have activities and events happening in the space.
All members are welcome to attend events that are listed with details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Civic Hall can also be reserved for [PRIVATE] meetings and events. These are listed here so we can all be aware ahead of time on what areas of the space will be in use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some events will require the community workspace to be cleared starting at 5:00pm. Please refer to this calendar for information on when and where these events will be happening. Keep your eyes open for signage!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>