<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Slack on Membership Guide</title>
    <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/slack/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Slack on Membership Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://membership-guide.civichall.org/tags/slack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack Community</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/membership/slack-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 07:43:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/membership/slack-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Slack network is an excellent platform to communicate and stay in touch with all of your fellow Civic Hall members. In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civic Hall Slack Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; we post events outside Civic Hall, share exciting member news, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shortly after your membership was approved, you should have received an email with an invitation to join the Slack channel. Create your login and you’re in. If you never received the invite, check your spam folder. If you still can not find it, email community@civichall.org and we will resend your invitation. Please make sure to provide an active email address.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Slack</title>
      <link>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/reference/how-to-use-slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 23:55:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://membership-guide.civichall.org/reference/how-to-use-slack/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Our Slack network is an excellent platform to communicate and stay in touch with all of your fellow Civic Hall Members. There’s a channel relevant to almost any interest, but not all of them have daily activity or conversation. Therefore, the community team here at Civic Hall thought it’d be convenient to analyze which Slack channels typically have the most activity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;rsquo;t see a channel that fits the topic of discussion you&amp;rsquo;d like to participate in, you can always create a new channel or, try to spark conversation in less active channels too! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, check the Slack Help website here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fslack.zendesk.com%2Fhc%2Fen-us&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNElgbiJI_aADmkxkeAFiJRXVwxrNQ&#34;&gt;https://slack.zendesk.com/hc/en-us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;slack-best-practices&#34;&gt;Slack Best Practices&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do&lt;/strong&gt; start channels for new interests groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Do not use @everyone&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; It will ping every user who is and isn&amp;rsquo;t on Slack at the time. The community team would like to reserve this tag &lt;strong&gt;for emergencies or important announcements.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do&lt;/strong&gt; use @here to grab the attention of members in the space or members of your channel. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt; use Slack to find people&amp;rsquo;s emails and add them to your newsletters without the members&amp;rsquo; consent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do&lt;/strong&gt; use Slack to reach out to fellow members you want to meet and collaborate with, especially if you forgot to exchange emails over coffee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt; use @channel in the #general channel. According to member feedback, this tends to be an unpopular action. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do&lt;/strong&gt; use @channel in special interest group channels if there is relative and important information you want to share with everyone in that channel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of our most popular Slack channels, as well as an idea of what type of conversation takes place in each of them:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/general/&#34;&gt;#general&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Conversation and shared articles covering a wide range of topics(mostly on what’s happening in civic tech) take place here. Daily reminders of upcoming events are provided here as well. Aside from the civic tech world, there have been discussions on politics and just technology in general.For example, the recent announcement of the Iphone 7, a post on September 13th being a Primary day for Democrat voters, and letters to congress. This is probably the most popular Slack channel, and definitely a great place to be able to get a discussion going!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/bookrecs/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#bookrecs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Lots of interesting book suggestions and recommendations from members in this channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/calltoaction/&#34;&gt;#calltoaction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/civicwomen/details/&#34;&gt;#civicwomen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/code/&#34;&gt;#code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  Discussion includes a few web links to articles revolving around issues that impact the coding world, as well as members seeking out partners/fellow coders to assist them with different projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/data/details/&#34;&gt;#data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/events-at-civichall/details/&#34;&gt;#events-at-civichall&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; RSS feed of all events and activities (published to our website) that are happening inside the community space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/events-outside-ch/&#34;&gt;#events-outside-ch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  A channel where members notify others about events happening outside of Civic Hall, such as a Black Lives Matter movement, an event promoting women in the tech world, or MeetUps of all sorts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/freefood/&#34;&gt;#freefood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  People notify other members of opportunities for free food that pop up, whether it’s in the cafe, or outside. (Definitely a channel to keep an eye on!) There tends to be opportunities for free bites to eat pretty often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/funding-_-opps/details/&#34;&gt;#funding-_-opps&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;Funding and Opportunities: Competitions, Grants, Accelerators, Incubators, nonprofit, grant writing tips, speaking/expert panel opps, funding panel opps., etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/hot-in-tech/details/&#34;&gt;#hot-in-tech&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;A slack channel for what’s hot in tech. Our favorite sources: reddit, stackoverflow, techcrunch, hackernews, AKA “those crazy people who think they are going to change the world &amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/internet-works/details/&#34;&gt;#internet-works &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/introduceyourself/details/&#34;&gt;#introduceyourself&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;Title says it all.  Leave your name, your company, and tell us a bit about yourself and the work you do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/jobs/&#34;&gt;#jobs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  Links to various job opportunities in civic tech are shared here. Good place to post if you’re either looking for opportunity, or looking for prospective employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/lookingfor/&#34;&gt;#lookingfor&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;Mostly members seeking out others for help in various areas, whether it be data experts, people to help with campaigns, etc. It can also be similar to the Jobs channel, in the sense that people also post here in search of new employees as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/lostandfound/&#34;&gt;#lostandfound&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;If we find something in the space that a member left behind, we post it on this channel. So make sure to check it out if you ever lose something at Civic Hall!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/politics/&#34;&gt;#politics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  Members engage in wide ranging political discussions. Article links are shared here as well. Recently there have been lots of content regarding the presidential candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/random/&#34;&gt;#random&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  One can find a member searching for help with a name for his cat, links to articles about the economy, art, and practically anything and everything (hence the title.) A good channel to use if you’d like to discuss a wide range of topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/security-hall/details/&#34;&gt;#security-hall&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;For Civic Hallers working around security (global, domestic, human, cyber, etc.) issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**
&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/show-and-tell/&#34;&gt;#showandtell&lt;/a&gt;**  A channel where members can share their work/projects for others to see. It provides an interesting opportunity to inform the Civic Hall Community of whatever work you’re up to, as well as the chance to find out a bit more about your fellow members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/sustainable-hall/details/&#34;&gt;#sustainable-hall&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;Ideas to reduce the environmental impact of Civic Hall and those who work here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://civichallmembers.slack.com/messages/the-suggestion-box/details/&#34;&gt;#the-suggestion-box&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;A place to throw out your crazy and most awesome ideas for making Civic Hall the coolest place on the planet. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>